<resources>
    <string name="app_name">TourismApp</string>
    <string name="title_activity_scrolling1">ScrollingActivity</string>
    <string name="large_text">

       "******A Guide for Kedarnath Trek******.\n\n"

        "**********Visit Kedarnath by Road (Till Sonprayag)***************.\n\n"

        "To reach at Kedarnath by road you need to book a taxi or bus service which can be privately "
        " or by the GMOU ltd. To reach at Kedarnath from Delhi you need to travel till Dehradun"
        " for which you can choose any medium be it road, rail or airways. From Dehradun travel"
        "till Haridwar and from Haridwar the following route will be your Guide to the Kedarnath Trek."

         "New Delhi to Haridwar 206km >> Haridwar to Rishikesh 24km >> Rishikesh to Devprayag 74km >> "
          "Devprayag to Srinagar 34km >> Srinagar to Rudraprayag 33km >> Rudraprayag to Gaurikund "
          "(via Tilwara-Agastmuni-Chandrapuri >> Kund >> Guptkashi >> Phata >> Sitapur >> Sonprayag) "
          "74km >> Gaurikund to Kedarnath  (by trek) 18km."

          "You can also visit Kedarnath from Delhi by boarding a direct bus from Delhi Bus Stand Kashmiri Gate to"
          "Gaurikund which is run by the Uttarakhand Transport Corporation. From Gaurikund further"
          "continue your trek to Kedarnath.\n\n"


       " ***********Visit Kedarnath by Air.***********\n\n"
       "To reach Kedarnath by air you can book a seat for yourself in a helicopter. If travelling by a"
        "helicopt44er till Kedarnath you can from Dehradun as well as Haridwar and Rishikesh."

       "From Dehradun- travel till the Shastradhara Helipad in Dehradun. The Helicopter will drop you "
        "at your destination within a time period of 40 minutes."

        "From Haridwar/Rishikesh- If you are planning to travel to Kedarnath from Rishikesh/Haridwar via "
        "Helicopter then travel from Haridwar/Rishikesh till Phata via taxi which is at an "
        "approx distance of 200km and 195km respectively.\n\n"

        "**************Kedarnath Trek Guide – How to Reach Kedarnath by Trek.**************************\n\n"
        "After you reach till Sonprayag you will have to travel in a shared cab which charges Rs 20per person"
        " this cab will take you till Gaurikund, Further from Gaurikund the trek toKedarnath begins"
        " the directions of which are listed below as your Guide to Kedarnath Trek.\n\n"

        "Kedarnath Trek Distance.\n\n"
        "The trek to Kedarnath is a 18 km trek which starts from Gaurikund till Kedarnath. The trek "
        "has changed since the 2013 flood disaster in Uttrakhand and since then the 14 km trek to"
        "Kedarnath has increased to a 16km trek..\n\n"

        "*************Route Map of the Kedarnath Trek.\n\n*************************"

        "The Kedarnath trek is a 18 km trek which starts from Gaurikund. Earlier the route followed"
        " was from Rambara, it was a well developed, well fenced and a facilitated trek route."
        " However the Gov has now changed the trek Route of Kedarnath after the 2013 disaster as "
        "the old trek route to Kedarnath was completely erased. The New Trek Route to Kedarnath "
        "is given below which will be your Travel Guide to Kedarnath Trek.\n\n "

        "Reach at Gaurikund (6km approx) through shared taxi from Sonprayag.\n\n"
        "Gaurikund to Jungle Chatti(6km) through the Rambara Bridge.\n\n"
        "Jungle Chatti to Bheembali (4km).\n\n"
        "Bheembali to Linchauli (3km).\n\n"
        "Linchauli to Kedarnath Base Camp (4km).\n\n"
        "Kedarnath Base Camp to Kedarnath Temple (1km).\n\n"

        "***************Features of the Kedarnath Trek.*************************\n\n"

        "The Kedarnath Trek is a 18km medium to steep trek which requires a good level of physical "
        "fitness. Before going for the trek every pilgrim has to get themselves checked that whether"
        "they are capable of trekking or not. Timings of Kedarnath Trek from Gaurikund commences "
        "from 04:00AM in the morning till 01:30PM. This timing is fixed because Kedarnath is located"
        "in the Kedarnath Wildlife Sanctuary and therefore the pilgrims are not allowed to trek anytime."
        "No pilgrim is allowed to leave after this specific time. These are high altitudes trek so it"
        "is advisory for the ones with respiratory problems to first consult with a doctor before trekking..\n\n"

        "****************Facilities at the Kedarnath Trek.*************************\n\n"

        "The Kedarnath Trek facilities include the services of Palki/Dandi, Kandi and Mule/Ponies. Anyone "
        "can book these services from the booking counter at Gaurikund/Sonprayag. Different distances"
        "have different rates such as the Gaurikund to Kedarnath Dandi will cost Rs 4450, Kandi will "
        "cost Rs 3350 and the Poni will cost Rs 4100. In the midst of the trek there are proper facilities"
        "of tented accommodation, drinking water and small shops/ restaurants are also there in the trek route."
        " There is also Helicopter services from the Kedarnath helipad to Phata and other helipads..\n\n"

        "***********************Things to Remember Before Going on the Kedarnath Trek.****************\n\n"

        "TDo get a check up before going on the trek to Kedarnath.\n\n"
        "People with Respiratory disorders and High Blood Pressure should not trek to Kedarnath.\n\n"
        "If you want to travel through Kandi, Ponies and Palki make sure that the prior booking is done at
        Gaurikund/Sonprayag booking counter.\n\n"
        "Trek between 04:00AM to 01:30PM as this is the only time when pilgrims are allowed to trek to Kedarnath.\n\n"
       "In case you won’t be able to cover the trek till late evening you can take Palki or Ponies to reach to your"
        "destination. You can also stay in the camps which are set up in between the trek at Jungle Chatti,"
        " Bheem Bali and Lincholi for a night and start journey next morning..\n\n"

        "So here is a Complete Guide to Kedarnath Trek for you which will help you to analyze and go for your"
        "Kedarnath Yatra, making it more divine and comfortable.\n\n"

    </string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="title_activity_scrolling">Kedarnath Trek</string>
    <string name="title_activity_scrolling2">ScrollingActivity</string>
</resources>